Kastle, Leonard; Papers ua902.021
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Instrumental Compositions, 1964-1992; Undated; 3; 2.74 cubic ft.
  - Concerto No. 1, 1980; Undated; 3.3
    - Muscians' Score, Bass, Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 4)
    - Muscians' Score, Bassoon and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 5)
    - Muscians' Score, Cello, Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 6)
    - Muscians' Score, Clarients and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 7)
    - Muscians' Score, Flutes, Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 8)
    - Muscians' Score, Harp, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 1)
    - Muscians' Score, Horns, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 2)
    - Muscians' Score, Oboes, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 3)
    - Muscians' Score, Percussion and Timpani, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 4)
    - Muscians' Score, Tombones and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 5)
    - Muscians' Score, Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 6)
    - Muscians' Score, Viola, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 7)
    - Muscians' Score, Violin 1, Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 8)
    - Muscians' Score, Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 1)
    - Original Manuscript, 1980 (Oversized 7, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Parts, Bass, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 3)
    - Tissues of Parts, Bassoons, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 4)
    - Tissues of Parts, Cello, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 5)
    - Tissues of Parts, Clarinets, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Parts, Flutes 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 7)
    - Tissues of Parts, Harp, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 8)
    - Tissues of Parts, Horns 1-4, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 9)
    - Tissues of Parts, Oboes, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 10)
    - Tissues of Parts, Percussion, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 11)
    - Tissues of Parts, Trombones and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 12)
    - Tissues of Parts, Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 13)
    - Tissues of Parts, Viola, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 14)
    - Tissues of Parts, Violin 1, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 15)
    - Tissues of Parts, Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 15)
    - Tissues of Parts, Orchestra Score, Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 1-4)
    - Tissues of Parts, Orchestra Score, Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Shaker Dances, 1985; 3.4
    - Manuscript Score for Capital Chamber Orchestra, 1985 (Oversized 10, Folder 1)
  - Romanza H.B., 1986; 3.5
    - Manuscript of Flute Score, 1986 (Oversized 10, Folder 2)
    - Orchestral Score, 1986 (Oversized 10, Folder 3)
  - Easter Sonata for Flute and Piano, 1987; 3.6
    - Manuscript Score, 1987 (Oversized 10, Folder 4)
    - Photocopy of Manuscript Score, 1987 (Oversized 10, Folder 5)
- Operas, 1950-1988; Undated; 4; 12.7 cubic ft.
  All the subseries in this series are arranged alphabetically.
  The fourth series contains musical and vocal compostions for the operas written by Kastle. Like Series 3, Series 4 is also broken down into subseries according to major works. Most of the subseries contain Masters of Parts, Blues of Parts, or Tissues of Parts as well as Orchestral Scores or Vocal Scores. A large amount of the material found in this series is undated.
  - The Swing, 1955; 4.1
    - Manuscript Score, 1955 (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
    - Tissues of Score, 1955 (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
  - Deseret, 1958-1959; Undated; 4.2
    - Deseret: An Opera in Three Acts, Undated; Similar versions of this bound bound book are also available. They remain unboxed due to their weight. (Oversized 21)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Bass, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Bassoon 1, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Bassoon 2, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Cello, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Cello, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Clarinet 1, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Clarinet 2, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 9)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Contra Bassoon, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 10)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Flute 1, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 11)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Flute 2, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 12)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Harp, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 13)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 14)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Box 1 (4-Operas), Folder 15)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Oboe 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Oboe 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 2)
    - Master of Parts, Act I, p.ercussion, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Trombone 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Trombone 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Trombone 3, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Trumpet 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Trumpet 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Tuba, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 9)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Viola, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 10)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Violin 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 11)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Violin 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 12)
    - Master of Parts, Act I Violin 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 13)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Bass, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 14)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Bassoon 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 15)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Bassoon 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 16)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Cello, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 17)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Clarinet 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 18)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Clarinet 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 19)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Contra Bassoon, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 20)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Flute 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 21)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Flute 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 22)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Harp, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 23)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 24)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 25)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Oboe 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 26)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Oboe 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 27)
    - Master of Parts, Act II, p.ercussion, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 28)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Trombone 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 29)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Trombone 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 30)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Trombone 3, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 31)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Trumpet 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 32)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Trumpet 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 33)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Tuba, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 34)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Viola, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 35)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Violin 1, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 36)
    - Master of Parts, Act II Violin 2, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 37)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Bass, Undated (Box 2 (4-Operas), Folder 38)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Bassoon 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Bassoon 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 2)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Cello, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Clarinet 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Clarinet 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Contra Bassoon, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Flute 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Flute 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Harp, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 9)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 10)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 11)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Oboe 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 12)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Oboe 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 13)
    - Master of Parts, Act III, p.ercussion, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 14)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Trombone 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 15)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Trombone 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 16)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Trombone 3, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 17)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Trumpet 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 18)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Trumpet 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 19)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Tuba, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 20)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Viola, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 21)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Violin 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 22)
    - Master of Parts, Act III Violin 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 23)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Bass, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 24-25)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Bassoon 1, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 26)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Bassoon 2, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 27)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Cello, Undated (Box 3 (4-Operas), Folder 28-30)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Clarinet 1, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Clarinet 2, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 2)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Contra Bassoon, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Flute 1, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Flute 2, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Harp, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Oboe 1, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 9)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Oboe 2 and English Horn, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 10)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Percussion 1, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 11)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Percussion 2, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 12)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Percussion 3, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 13)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Percussion 4, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 14)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Trombone 1, Undated (Box 4 (4-Operas), Folder 15)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Trombone 2, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Trombone 3, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 2)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Trumpet 1, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Trumpet 2, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Tuba, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Viola 1, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Viola 2, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Viola 3, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Violin 1, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 9-10)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Violin 2, Undated (Box 5 (4-Operas), Folder 11-12)
    - Musicians' Scores, Acts I-III Violin 2, Undated (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 1-2)
    - Orchestral Score, Act I, p. 1-200, Undated (Oversized 13, Folder 1)
    - Orchestral Score, Act I, p. 201-399, Undated (Oversized 13, Folder 2)
    - Orchestral Score, Act II, p. 400-550, Undated (Oversized 13, Folder 3)
    - Orchestral Score, Act II, p. 551-713, Undated (Oversized 14, Folder 1)
    - Orchestral Score, Act III, p. 713-845, Undated (Oversized 14, Folder 2)
    - Orchestral Score, Act III, p. 846-973, Undated (Oversized 14, Folder 3)
    - Original Piano-Voice Manuscript, Act I, 1958 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Original Piano-Voice Manuscript, Act II, 1959 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Original Piano-Voice Manuscript, Act III, Undated (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Piano-Vocal, Act I, Undated (Oversized 19, Folder 1)
    - Piano-Vocal, Act I (Early Version), Undated (Oversized 19, Folder 2)
    - Piano-Vocal, Act II, Undated (Oversized 19, Folder 3-6)
    - Piano-Vocal, Act I-III, 1959 (Oversized 20, Folder 1)
    - Piano-Vocal, Act I-III, 1959 (Oversized 20, Folder 2)
    - Vocal Score, Act I, Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 1)
    - Vocal Score, Act II, Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 2)
    - Vocal Score, Act III, Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 3)
    - Vocal Parts, Act I, Mr. and Mrs. Webb, p. 11-13, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 1)
    - Vocal Parts, Act I, Ann, p. 28-16, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 2)
    - Vocal Parts, Act I, Ann, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 3)
    - Vocal Parts, Act I, Brigham, p. 53-70, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 4)
    - Vocal Parts, Ann and James, p. 146-176, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 5)
    - Vocal Parts, Act II, Sarah, p. 212-217, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 6)
    - Vocal Parts, Acts II-III, James, Undated (Oversized 15, Folder 7)
    - Vocal Parts, Acts I-III, Sarah, 1959 (Oversized 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Vocal Parts, Acts I-III, Mrs. Webb, Undated (Oversized 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Vocal Parts, Acts I-III, Mr. Webb, Undated (Oversized 16, Folder 5)
    - Vocal Parts, Acts I-III, James, 1959 (Oversized 17, Folder 1)
    - Vocal Parts, Piano-Vocal, Act I, Undated (Oversized 17, Folder 2)
    - Vocal Parts, Piano-Vocal, Act II, Undated (Oversized 17, Folder 3)
    - Vocal Parts, Piano-Vocal, Act III, 1959 (Oversized 17, Folder 4)
  - The Pariahs, 1950; 1961-1969; Undated; 4.3
    - Acts I-III, Undated (Oversized 41)
    - Acts I and II, 1976 (Oversized 41)
    - Acts II-III, Undated (Oversized 42)
    - Acts I-III, Undated (Oversized 43)
    - Act III, Undated (Oversized 40, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Basson, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Contra Basson, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Percussion, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Trombone 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue, Trumpet, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I Bass, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I Cello, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I English horn, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I Harp, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene 1 Oboes 1, 2, and 3, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I Viola, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I Violin 1, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Prologue and Act I Scene I Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Bass, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Basson, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Cello, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Harps, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 17)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 18)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Oboe, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 19)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Percussion, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 20)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Trombones and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 21)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 22)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Viola, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 23)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Violin, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 24)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene II Vocals, Undated (Oversized 25, Folder 25)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Bass, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Basson, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Cello, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Harp, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III English Horn, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Oboe, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Percussion, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Trombones 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Viola, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene III Vocal, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Bass Clarinet and Clarinets 1, 2, and 3, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 17)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Bassons, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 18)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Cello, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 19)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Contrabasson, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 20)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 21)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 22)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Oboes, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 23)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Percussion, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 24)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Trombones and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 26, Folder 25)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Trumpets 1-4, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Act I Scene IV Viola, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Violin I, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Bass, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Basson and Contra Basson, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Cello, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Clarinet and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Flute, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Harp, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Horns 1-4, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Oboe and English, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Percussion, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Trombones and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Viola, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene I Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Bass, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 17)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Bassoon 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 18)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Bassoon 3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 19)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Cello, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 20)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Clarinet and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 27, Folder 21)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II English Horn, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Flutes and Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Harps, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Oboes, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Percussion, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Trombones 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Viola, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene II Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Bass, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Bassoon and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Cello, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Clarinets, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Flute, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 17)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 18)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 19)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Oboes, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 20)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Piano and Vocals, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 21)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Trombones, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 22)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 23)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Viola, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 24)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene III Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 28, Folder 25)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Bass, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Bassoons 1 and 2 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Clarinets 1-3 and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Flutes 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Horns 1 and 2, Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Oboes 1 and 2 and English Horn, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Percussion, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Trumpets 1-4, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 9)